<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Profit's Blog</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/</link><description>Recent content on Profit's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</managingEditor><webMaster>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertmprofit.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Directory Number Update with Postman</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2025-05-09-using-postman-for-cucm-updates/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2025-05-09-using-postman-for-cucm-updates/</guid><description>&lt;p>You&amp;rsquo;re halfway through the workweek and there&amp;rsquo;s an emergency, a customer needs to migrate thousands numbers from one partition to another or migrate to a new number altogether within 48 hours. What do you do? &lt;em>Hint: Not Panic&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Unable to Call Forward All (CFA) from Phones</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2025-02-01-call-forwarding-not-working/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2025-02-01-call-forwarding-not-working/</guid><description>&lt;p>Issues in production are the gifts that keep on giving. Another strange one to look at as phones were unable to perform Call Forwarding All (CFA) from phones, depending on which server they were registered to.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dial Peers Unencrypted Post Upgrade</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-10-11-dial_peers_unencrypted_post_xe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-10-11-dial_peers_unencrypted_post_xe/</guid><description>&lt;p>I ran in to an issue in a customer&amp;rsquo;s production environment a few months back with a voice stream not negotiating Secure Real Time Transport Protocol (SRTP) even though it was configured correctly on the customer&amp;rsquo;s edge router, or so we thought.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SSM On-Prem Upgrade Issue: "No Matching MAC Found"</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-08-19-ssm_on-prem_upgrade_issue_no_matching_mac_found/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-08-19-ssm_on-prem_upgrade_issue_no_matching_mac_found/</guid><description>&lt;p>This document provides step-by-step instructions for upgrading Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Smart Software Manager (SSM) On-Prem from version 7-202001 to 8-202102, addressing common issues like Message Authentication Code (MAC) mismatches and using SFTP for file transfers.&lt;br>
I wrote this a while back when running in to issues in a production environment and am finally posting in case others run in to this while preparing for their Alma Linux upgrades. See my other post for those upgrade steps.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cisco Smart Satellite Manager (SSM) Server AlmaLinux Upgrade Overview</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-07-22-satellite_server_almalinux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-07-22-satellite_server_almalinux/</guid><description>&lt;p>As most of the other Cisco Unified Communications products are requiring migration from the underlying CentOS to AlmaLinux, the on-premises satellite license server is no exception. Here are a few high level steps needed in order to migrate.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Using TCL to Update E164 Pattern Maps</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-07-15-using-tcl-pattern-map/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-07-15-using-tcl-pattern-map/</guid><description>&lt;p>This document details using Tool Command Language (TCL) for managing dynamic E164-pattern-maps on routers, focusing on migration scenarios with frequent, noncontiguous number block changes. It outlines syntax and methodologies to optimize handling these updates, ensuring seamless modifications during transitions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/blocking-numbers-with-e164-pattern-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/blocking-numbers-with-e164-pattern-maps/</guid><description>#Working Dial Peer
dial-peer voice 3000 voip description SIP from BT translation-profile incoming BT-Inbound-Translation preference 5 session protocol sipv2 answer-address .T voice-class codec 1 voice-class sip copy-list 3000 voice-class sip bind control source-interface GigabitEthernet0/0/1 voice-class sip bind media source-interface GigabitEthernet0/0/1 voice-class sip audio forced dtmf-relay rtp-nte no vad voice class e164-pattern-map 3001 url http://&amp;lt;server&amp;gt;/pattern-map.cfg or
voice class e164-pattern-map 3001 url http://&amp;lt;server&amp;gt;/pattern-map.txt voice translation-rule 3001 rule 1 reject /.*/ voice translation-profile BT-Inbound-CallBlock translate calling 3001 dial-peer voice 3002 voip description SIP from ISP translation-profile incoming BT-Inbound-Translation call-block translation-profile incoming BT-Inbound-CallBlock call-block disconnect-cause incoming call-reject session protocol sipv2 incoming calling e164-pattern-map 3001 voice-class codec 1 voice-class sip bind control source-interface GigabitEthernet0/0/1 voice-class sip bind media source-interface GigabitEthernet0/0/1 voice-class sip audio forced dtmf-relay rtp-nte no vad</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/page/about/</guid><description>Hello there!
Before joining Cisco, I spent several years as a network engineer supporting production environments and managing a training and test lab. This role afforded me the invaluable opportunity to lead a quarterly two-week course on Professional-level Route/Switch/UC topics.
Over the past nine years at Cisco, my role has spanned multiple networks and regions, where I&amp;rsquo;ve been responsible for the complete lifecycle of customer engagements—from demonstrating the potential of Cisco software management to securing follow-on orders.</description></item></channel></rss>