<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Profit's Blog</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/</link><description>Recent content on Profit's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</managingEditor><webMaster>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robertmprofit.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using TCL to Update E164 Pattern Maps</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-07-15-using-tcl-pattern-map/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/post/2024-07-15-using-tcl-pattern-map/</guid><description>Using TCL for E164-Pattern-Map Modification Contents Using TCL for E164-Pattern-Map Modification Contents Introduction Prerequisites Components Used Important Create Initial Pattern-Map File and Load into Memory - Detailed Explanation File Creation Example with Data Append Data to an Existing File Example: Create the File and Remove a Single Line or Pattern Creating the file Removing a Single Line from the File Removing Entries Remove a Single Line from an Existing File Detailed Explanation Remove Multiple Single Entries Detailed Explanation Use RegEx to Match Multiple Numbers Match an Entry with Wild Cards Present Example: Removing Multiple Lines from a File Appendix Result of Not Reloading the Modified File Carriage Returns are Acceptable in a Pattern-Map Introduction This document provides a detailed overview of utilizing Tool Command Language (TCL) for the effective management of dynamic E164-pattern-maps stored locally on routers.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://robertmprofit.com/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>robert.profit82@gmail.com (Robert Profit)</author><guid>https://robertmprofit.com/page/about/</guid><description>Hello there!
My name is Robert Profit and I have been in the IT field for close to 20 years now. First serving in the U.S. Army in communications supporting radios and phones. Later on, supporting routers, switches, and Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Call Manager.
Afterwards, I became a Network Engineer supporting communications systems integration and teaching quarterly classes on CCNP level Route-Switch and Voice topics.
Now, I have been at Cisco close to nine years supporting their entire porfolio of Unified Communiciations solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>